https://www.hrcatholicschool.org/privacy-policy

FacebookTwitterLinkedin
Search:
Search
QuicklinksHomeDonateClasslinkRenWeb Gradebook
About HRWelcome MessageSchool FactsVirtual TourDirectionsOur StaffOur School DirectoryCareer OpportunitiesAcademicsCurriculumGrade Level InformationTechnologyGuidanceMedia CenterClasslinkFaith LifeOur Religion ProgramServiceSpiritual Life ProgramProgramsAcademic Honor SocietiesAftercareAdmissionsHow to ApplyNew Student RegistrationFAQTuitionFinancial AidAdvancementDonate NowEventsAnnual FundAlumniGrandparentsGalaAnnual ReportsAlumniNewsEventsUpdate Us
Mission Statement
Holy Redeemer Catholic School is a faith-centered community dedicated to the Catholic Tradition rooted in the Gospel of Jesus Christ. Our school challenges students to reach their full potential in academics, character and faith.
Privacy Statement
Thank you for visiting the Holy Redeemer Catholic School website. Your privacy is very important to us. Our policy is to collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our website unless you actively choose to make such information available to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information (name, email address, class year, mailing address, phone number), it will not be disclosed to third parties for any reason. Information collected is used to provide you with access to restricted areas of our site by creating a profile and password unique to you. Passwords are only given to Holy Redeemer constituents. If you choose to make a donation online or register for an event and provide us with personal information, that information will only be used to process your request. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us.
About HRWelcome MessageSchool FactsVirtual TourDirectionsOur StaffOur School DirectoryCareer OpportunitiesAcademicsCurriculumGrade Level InformationTechnologyGuidanceMedia CenterClasslinkFaith LifeOur Religion ProgramServiceSpiritual Life ProgramProgramsAcademic Honor SocietiesAftercareAdmissionsHow to ApplyNew Student RegistrationFAQTuitionFinancial AidAdvancementDonate NowEventsAnnual FundAlumniGrandparentsGalaAnnual ReportsAlumniNewsEventsUpdate Us
Apply NowStay In TouchDonate
" Holy Redeemer is our kids' second home. The teachers and administrators treat our kids as if they are their own."
- Michelle Wise, Parent
About UsAcademicsFaith LifeProgramsAdmissionsAdvancementAlumni
3380 Old Alabama Road, Johns Creek, GA 30022-5053  |  Phone: 770-410-4056  |Fax: 770-410-1454   |  Email:info@hrcatholicschool.org
Copyright 2014 Holy Redeemer Catholic School  |  Privacy Policy  |  Contact Us | Webmail  | Classlink | Login
